New York State Department of State Bureau of Miscellaneous Records Enrolled Acts of the State Legislature
New York State Archives
- Original Laws 1837 Chapters 362-478 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 162)
- Original Laws 1838 Chapters 1-84, 13036-78 (Volume 163)
- Original Laws 1838 Chapters 85-169, 13036-78 (Volume 164)
- Original Laws 1838 Chapters 170-255, 13036-78 (Volume 165)
- Original Laws 1838 Chapters 256-333 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 166)
- Original Laws 1839 Chapters 1-98, 13036-78 (Volume 167)
- Original Laws 1839 Chapters 99-198, 13036-78 (Volume 168)
- Original Laws 1839 Chapters 199-293, 13036-78 (Volume 169)
- Original Laws 1839 Chapters 294-390 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 170)
- Original Laws 1840 Chapters 1-100, 13036-78 (Volume 171)
- Original Laws 1840 Chapters 101-201, 13036-78 (Volume 172)
- Original Laws 1840 missing, 13036-78 (Volume 173)
- Vol. 174, 13036-78 (Volume 174)
- Original Laws 1841 Chapters 1-90, 13036-78 (Volume 175)
- Original Laws 1841 Chapters 91-180, 13036-78 (Volume 176)
- Original Laws 1841 Chapters 181-272, 13036-78 (Volume 177)
- Original Laws 1841 Chapters 273-351 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 178)
- Original Laws 1842 Chapters 1-94, 13036-78 (Volume 179)
- Original Laws 1842 Chapters 95-170, 13036-78 (Volume 180)
- Original Laws 1842 Chapters 171-255, 13036-78 (Volume 181)
- Original Laws 1842 Chapters 256-326 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 182)
- Original Laws 1843 Chapters 1-91, 13036-78 (Volume 183)
- Original Laws 1843 Chapters 92-166, 13036-78 (Volume 184)
- Original Laws 1843 Chapters 167-240 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 185)
- Original Laws 1844 Chapters 1-100, 13036-78 (Volume 186)
- Original Laws 1844 Chapters 101-180, 13036-78 (Volume 187)
- Original Laws 1844 Chapters 181-275, 13036-78 (Volume 188)
- Original Laws 1844 Chapters 276-347 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 189)
- Original Laws 1845 Chapters 1-94, 13036-78 (Volume 190)
- Original Laws 1845 Chapters 95-183, 13036-78 (Volume 191)
- Original Laws 1845 Chapters 184-279, 13036-78 (Volume 192)
- Original Laws 1845 Chapters 280-367 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 193)
- Original Laws 1846 Chapters 1-92, 13036-78 (Volume 194)
- Original Laws 1846 Chapters 93-186, 13036-78 (Volume 195)
- Original Laws 1846 Chapters 187-269, 13036-78 (Volume 196)
- Original Laws 1846 Chapters 270-337 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 197)
- Original Laws 1847 Chapters 1-85, 13036-78 (Volume 198)
- Original Laws 1847 Chapters 86-170, 13036-78 (Volume 199)
- Original Laws 1847 Chapters 171-255, 13036-78 (Volume 200)
- Original Laws 1847 Chapters 256-340, 13036-78 (Volume 201)
- Original Laws 1847 Chapters 341-433, 13036-78 (Volume 202)
- Original Laws 1847 Chapters 434-499 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 203)
- Original Laws 1848 Chapters 1-105, 13036-78 (Volume 204)
- Original Laws 1848 Chapters 106-200, 13036-78 (Volume 205)
- Original Laws 1848 Chapters 201-299, 13036-78 (Volume 206)
- Original Laws 1848 Chapters 300-381 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 207)
- Original Laws 1849 Chapters 1-87, 13036-78 (Volume 208)
- Original Laws 1849 Chapters 88-170, 13036-78 (Folder 209)
- Original Laws 1849 Chapters 171-240, 13036-78 (Volume 210)
- Original Laws 1849 Chapters 241-319, 13036-78 (Volume 211)
- Original Laws 1849 Chapters 320-399, 13036-78 (Volume 212)
- Original Laws 1849 Chapters 400-439 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 213)
- Original Laws 1850 Chapters 1-80, 13036-78 (Volume 214)
- Original Laws 1850 Chapters 81-140, 13036-78 (Volume 215)
- Original Laws 1850 Chapters 141-201, 13036-78 (Volume 216)
- Original Laws 1850 Chapters 202-261, 13036-78 (Volume 217)
- Original Laws 1850 Chapters 262-309, 13036-78 (Volume 218)
- Original Laws 1850 Chapters 310-378 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 219)
- Original Laws 1851 Chapters 1-90, 13036-78 (Volume 220)
- Original Laws 1851 Chapters 91-137, 13036-78 (Volume 221)
- Original Laws 1851 Chapters 138-205, 13036-78 (Volume 222)
- Original Laws 1851 Chapters 206-264, 13036-78 (Volume 223)
- Original Laws 1851 Chapters 265-338, 13036-78 (Volume 224)
- Original Laws 1851 Chapters 339-401, 13036-78 (Volume 225)
- Original Laws 1851 Chapters 402-479, 13036-78 (Volume 226)
- Original Laws 1851 Chapters 480-547 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 227)
- Original Laws 1852 Chapters 1-85, 13036-78 (Volume 228)
- Original Laws 1852 Chapters 86-150, 13036-78 (Volume 229)
- Original Laws 1852 Chapters 151-225, 13036-78 (Volume 230)
- Original Laws 1852 Chapters 226-287, 13036-78 (Volume 231)
- Original Laws 1852 Chapters 288-355, 13036-78 (Volume 232)
- Original Laws 1852 Chapters 356-408 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 233)
- Original Laws 1853 Chapters 1-88, 13036-78 (Volume 235)
- Original Laws 1853 Chapters 89-143, 13036-78 (Volume 236)
- Original Laws 1853 Chapters 144-210, 13036-78 (Volume 237)
- Original Laws 1853 Chapters 211-276, 13036-78 (Volume 238)
- Original Laws 1853 Chapters 277-341, 13036-78 (Volume 239)
- Original Laws 1853 Chapters 342-432, 13036-78 (Volume 240)
- Original Laws 1853 Chapters 433-502, 13036-78 (Volume 241)
- Original Laws 1853 Chapters 503-583, 13036-78 (Volume 242)
- Original Laws 1853 Chapters 584-654 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 243)
- Original Laws 1854 Chapters 1-75, 13036-78 (Volume 244)
- Original Laws 1854 Chapters 76-135, 13036-78 (Volume 245)
- Original Laws 1854 Chapters 136-219, 13036-78 (Volume 246)
- Original Laws 1854 Chapters 220-304, 13036-78 (Volume 247)
- Original Laws 1854 Chapters 305-383, 13036-78 (Volume 248)
- Original Laws 1854 Chapters 384-403 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 249)
- Original Laws 1855 Chapters 1-96, 13036-78 (Volume 250)
- Original Laws 1855 Chapters 97-183, 13036-78 (Volume 251)
- Original Laws 1855 Chapters 184-263, 13036-78 (Volume 252)
- Original Laws 1855 Chapters 264-336, 13036-78 (Volume 253)
- Original Laws 1855 Chapters 337-416, 13036-78 (Volume 254)
- Original Laws 1855 Chapters 417-502, 13036-78 (Volume 255)
- Original Laws 1855 Chapters 503-576 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 256)
- Original Laws 1856 Chapters 1-74, 13036-78 (Volume 257)
- Original Laws 1856 Chapters 75-146, 13036-78 (Volume 258)
- Original Laws 1856 Chapters 147-205 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 260)
- Original Laws 1857 Chapters 1-66, 13036-78 (Volume 261)
- Original Laws 1857 Chapters 67-144, 13036-78 (Volume 262)
- Original Laws 1857 Chapters 145-201, 13036-78 (Volume 263)
- Original Laws 1857 Chapters 202-286, 13036-78 (Volume 264)
- Original Laws 1857 Chapters 287-349, 13036-78 (Volume 265)
- Original Laws 1857 Chapters 350-425, 13036-78 (Volume 266)
- Original Laws 1857 Chapters 426-499, 13036-78 (Volume 267)
- Original Laws 1857 Chapters 500-561, 13036-78 (Volume 268)
- Original Laws 1857 Chapters 562-621, 13036-78 (Volume 269)
- Original Laws 1857 Chapters 622-689, 13036-78 (Volume 270)
- Original Laws 1857 Chapters 690-764, 13036-78 (Volume 271)
- Original Laws 1857 Chapters 765-804 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 272)
- Original Laws 1858 Chapters 1-77, 13036-78 (Volume 273)
- Original Laws 1858 Chapters 78-162, 13036-78 (Volume 274)
- Original Laws 1858 Chapters 163-246, 13036-78 (Volume 275)
- Original Laws 1858 Chapters 247-326, 13036-78 (Volume 276)
- Original Laws 1858 Chapters 327-376 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 277)
- Original Laws 1859 Chapters 1-65, 13036-78 (Volume 278)
- Original Laws 1859 Chapters 66-135, 13036-78 (Volume 279)
- Original Laws 1859 Chapters 136-222, 13036-78 (Volume 280)
- Original Laws 1859 Chapters 223-279, 13036-78 (Volume 281)
- Original Laws 1859 Chapters 280-336, 13036-78 (Volume 282)
- Original Laws 1859 Chapters 337-399, 13036-78 (Volume 283)
- Original Laws 1859 Chapters 400-453, 13036-78 (Volume 284)
- Original Laws 1859 Chapters 454-513 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 285)
- Original Laws 1860 Chapters 1-74, 13036-78 (Volume 286)
- Original Laws 1860 Chapters 75-148 (missing from shelf), 13036-78 (Volume 287)
- Original Laws 1860 Chapters 149-216, 13036-78 (Volume 288)
- Original Laws 1860 Chapters 217-287, 13036-78 (Volume 289)
- Original Laws 1860 Chapters 288-363, 13036-78 (Volume 290)
- Original Laws 1860 Chapters 364-430, 13036-78 (Volume 291)
- Original Laws 1860 Chapters 431-470, 13036-78 (Volume 292)
- Original Laws 1860 Chapters 471-524 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 293)
- Original Laws 1861 Chapters 1-72, 13036-78 (Volume 294)
- Original Laws 1861 Chapters 73-142, 13036-78 (Volume 295)
- Original Laws 1861 Chapters 143-160, 13036-78 (Volume 296)
- Original Laws 1861 Chapters 161-237, 13036-78 (Volume 297)
- Original Laws 1861 Chapters 238-299, 13036-78 (Volume 298)
- Original Laws 1861 Chapters 300-340 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 299)
- Original Laws 1862 Chapters 1-51, 13036-78 (Volume 300)
- Original Laws 1862 Chapters 52-127, 13036-78 (Volume 301)
- Original Laws 1862 Chapters 128-211, 13036-78 (Volume 302)
- Original Laws 1862 Chapters 212-289, 13036-78 (Volume 303)
- Original Laws 1862 Chapters 290-357, 13036-78 (Volume 304)
- Original Laws 1862 Chapters 358-406, 13036-78 (Volume 305)
- Original Laws 1862 Chapters 407-461, 13036-78 (Volume 306)
- Original Laws 1862 Chapters 462-489 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 307)
- Original Laws 1863 Chapters 1-68, 13036-78 (Volume 308)
- Original Laws 1863 Chapters 69-125, 13036-78 (Volume 309)
- Original Laws 1863 Chapters 126-180, 13036-78 (Volume 310)
- Original Laws 1863 Chapters 181-232, 13036-78 (Volume 311)
- Original Laws 1863 Chapters 233-290, 13036-78 (Volume 312)
- Original Laws 1863 Chapters 291-358, 13036-78 (Volume 313)
- Original Laws 1863 Chapters 359-403, 13036-78 (Volume 314)
- Original Laws 1863 Chapters 404-462, 13036-78 (Volume 315)
- Original Laws 1863 Chapters 463-515 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 316)
- Original Laws 1864 Chapters 1-80, 13036-78 (Volume 317)
- Original Laws 1864 Chapters 81-138, 13036-78 (Volume 318)
- Original Laws 1864 Chapters 139-188, 13036-78 (Volume 319)
- Original Laws 1864 Chapters 189-247, 13036-78 (Volume 320)
- Original Laws 1864 Chapters 248-277, 13036-78 (Volume 321)
- Original Laws 1864 Chapters 278-346, 13036-78 (Volume 322)
- Original Laws 1864 Chapters 347-404, 13036-78 (Volume 323)
- Original Laws 1864 Chapters 405-458, 13036-78 (Volume 324)
- Original Laws 1864 Chapters 459-547, 13036-78 (Volume 325)
- Original Laws 1864 Chapters 548-596 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 326)
- Original Laws 1865 Chapters 1-88, 13036-78 (Volume 327)
- Original Laws 1865 Chapters 89-165, 13036-78 (Volume 328)
- Original Laws 1865 Chapters 166-251, 13036-78 (Volume 329)
- Original Laws 1865 Chapters 252-334, 13036-78 (Volume 330)
- Original Laws 1865 Chapters 335-382, 13036-78 (Volume 331)
- Original Laws 1865 Chapters 383-462, 13036-78 (Volume 332)
- Original Laws 1865 Chapters 463-540, 13036-78 (Volume 333)
- Original Laws 1865 Chapters 541-569, 13036-78 (Volume 334)
- Original Laws 1865 Chapters 570-634, 13036-78 (Volume 335)
- Original Laws 1865 Chapters 635-720, 13036-78 (Volume 336)
- Original Laws 1865 Chapters 721-780 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 337)
- Original Laws 1866 Chapters 1-74, 13036-78 (Volume 338)
- Original Laws 1866 Chapters 75-143, 13036-78 (Volume 339)
- Original Laws 1866 Chapters 144-213, 13036-78 (Volume 340)
- Original Laws 1866 Chapters 214-274, 13036-78 (Volume 341)
- Original Laws 1866 Chapters 275-334, 13036-78 (Volume 342)
- Original Laws 1866 Chapters 335-405, 13036-78 (Volume 343)
- Original Laws 1866 Chapters 406-476, 13036-78 (Volume 344)
- Original Laws 1866 Chapters 477-548, 13036-78 (Volume 345)
- Original Laws 1866 Chapters 549-624, 13036-78 (Volume 346)
- Original Laws 1866 Chapters 625-691, 13036-78 (Volume 347)
- Original Laws 1866 Chapters 692-748, 13036-78 (Volume 348)
- Original Laws 1866 Chapters 749-800, 13036-78 (Volume 349)
- Original Laws 1866 Chapters 801-835, 13036-78 (Volume 350)
- Original Laws 1866 Chapters 836-873, 13036-78 (Volume 351)
- Original Laws 1866 Chapters 874-916 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 352)
- Original Laws 1867 Chapters 1-86, 13036-78 (Volume 353)
- Original Laws 1867 Chapters 87-161, 13036-78 (Volume 354)
- Original Laws 1867 Chapters 162-231, 13036-78 (Volume 355)
- Original Laws 1867 Chapters 232-287, 13036-78 (Volume 356)
- Original Laws 1867 Chapters 288-329, 13036-78 (Volume 358)
- Original Laws 1867 Chapters 330-383, 13036-78 (Volume 359)
- Original Laws 1867 Chapters 384-422, 13036-78 (Volume 360)
- Original Laws 1867 Chapters 423-471, 13036-78 (Volume 361)
- Original Laws 1867 Chapters 472-503, 13036-78 (Volume 362)
- Original Laws 1867 Chapters 504-527, 13036-78 (Volume 363)
- Original Laws 1867 Chapters 528-587, 13036-78 (Volume 364)
- Original Laws 1867 Chapters 588-663, 13036-78 (Volume 365)
- Original Laws 1867 Chapters 664-736, 13036-78 (Volume 366)
- Original Laws 1867 Chapters 737-788, 13036-78 (Volume 367)
- Original Laws 1867 Chapters 789-835, 13036-78 (Volume 368)
- Original Laws 1867 Chapters 836-892, 13036-78 (Volume 369)
- Original Laws 1867 Chapters 893-941, 13036-78 (Volume 370)
- Original Laws 1867 Chapters 942-974 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 371)
- Original Laws 1868 Chapters 1 -66, 13036-78 (Volume 372)
- Original Laws 1868 Chapters 67-135, 13036-78 (Volume 373)
- Original Laws 1868 Chapters 136-178, 13036-78 (Volume 374)
- Original Laws 1868 Chapters 179-249, 13036-78 (Volume 375)
- Original Laws 1868 Chapters 250-310, 13036-78 (Volume 376)
- Original Laws 1868 Chapters 311-368, 13036-78 (Volume 377)
- Original Laws 1868 Chapters 369-441, 13036-78 (Volume 378)
- Original Laws 1868 Chapters 442-501, 13036-78 (Volume 379)
- Original Laws 1868 Chapters 502-571, 13036-78 (Volume 380)
- Original Laws 1868 Chapters 572-631, 13036-78 (Volume 381)
- Original Laws 1868 Chapters 632-673, 13036-78 (Volume 382)
- Original Laws 1868 Chapters 674-738, 13036-78 (Volume 383)
- Original Laws 1868 Chapters 739-799, 13036-78 (Volume 384)
- Original Laws 1868 Chapters 800-834, 13036-78 (Volume 385)
- Original Laws 1868 Chapters 835 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 386)
- Original Laws 1869 Chapters 1-60, 13036-78 (Volume 387)
- Original Laws 1869 Chapters 61-112, 13036-78 (Volume 388)
- Original Laws 1869 Chapters 113-164, 13036-78 (Volume 389)
- Original Laws 1869 Chapters 165-216, 13036-78 (Volume 390)
- Original Laws 1869 Chapters 217-272, 13036-78 (Volume 391)
- Original Laws 1869 Chapters 273-300, 13036-78 (Volume 392)
- Original Laws 1869 Chapters 301- 336, 13036-78 (Volume 393)
- Original Laws 1869 Chapters 337-392, 13036-78 (Volume 394)
- Original Laws 1869 Chapters 393-452, 13036-78 (Volume 395)
- Original Laws 1869 Chapters 453-485, 13036-78 (Volume 396)
- Original Laws 1869 Chapters 486-524, 13036-78 (Volume 397)
- Original Laws 1869 Chapters 525-573, 13036-78 (Volume 398)
- Original Laws 1869 Chapters 574-621, 13036-78 (Volume 399)
- Original Laws 1869 Chapters 622-679, 13036-78 (Volume 400)
- Original Laws 1869 Chapters 680-714, 13036-78 (Volume 401)
- Original Laws 1869 Chapters 715-765, 13036-78 (Volume 402)
- Original Laws 1869 Chapters 766-821, 13036-78 (Volume 403)
- Original Laws 1869 Chapters 822-837, 13036-78 (Volume 404)
- Original Laws 1869 Chapters 838-877, 13036-78 (Volume 405)
- Original Laws 1869 Chapters 878-901, 13036-78 (Volume 406)
- Original Laws 1869 Chapters 902-920 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 407)
- Original Laws 1870 Chapters 1-32, 13036-78 (Volume 408)
- Original Laws 1870 Chapters 33-77, 13036-78 (Volume 409)
- Original Laws 1870 Chapters 78-105, 13036-78 (Volume 410)
- Original Laws 1870 Chapters 106-143, 13036-78 (Volume 411)
- Original Laws 1870 Chapters 144-205, 13036-78 (Volume 412)
- Original Laws 1870 Chapters 206-262, 13036-78 (Volume 413)
- Original Laws 1870 Chapters 263-291, 13036-78 (Volume 414)
- Original Laws 1870 Chapters 292-345, 13036-78 (Volume 415)
- Original Laws 1870 Chapters 346-383, 13036-78 (Volume 416)
- Original Laws 1870 Chapters 384-455, 13036-78 (Volume 417)
- Original Laws 1870 Chapters 456-495, 13036-78 (Volume 418)
- Original Laws 1870 Chapters 496-520, 13036-78 (Volume 419)
- Original Laws 1870 Chapters 521-578, 13036-78 (Volume 420)
- Original Laws 1870 Chapters 579-623, 13036-78 (Volume 421)
- Original Laws 1870 Chapters 624-673, 13036-78 (Volume 422)
- Original Laws 1870 Chapters 674-693, 13036-78 (Volume 423)
- Original Laws 1870 Chapters 694-719, 13036-78 (Volume 424)
- Original Laws 1870 Chapters 720-762, 13036-78 (Volume 425)
- Original Laws 1870 Chapters 763-784, 13036-78 (Volume 426)
- Original Laws 1870 Chapters 785-808 and Resolutions, 13036-78 (Volume 427)
- Original Laws 1871 Chapters 1-150, 13036-78 (Volume 428)
- Original Laws 1871 Chapters 151-299, 13036-78 (Volume 429)
- Original Laws 1871 Chapters 300-460, 13036-78 (Volume 430)
- Original Laws 1871 Chapters 461-579, 13036-78 (Volume 431)
- Original Laws 1871 Chapters 580-715, 13036-78 (Volume 432)
- Original Laws 1871 Chapters 716 -826, 13036-78 (Volume 433)
- Original Laws 1871 Chapters 827-946, 13036-78 (Volume 434)
- Original Laws 1872 Chapters 129-239, 13036-78 (Volume 436)
- Original Laws 1872 Chapters 1-128, 13036-78 (Volume 435)
- Original Laws 1872 Chapters 240-386, 13036-78 (Volume 437)
- Original Laws 1872 Chapters 387-540, 13036-78 (Volume 438)
- Original Laws 1872 Chapters 541-655, 13036-78 (Volume 439)
- Original Laws 1872 Chapters 656-775, 13036-78 (Volume 440)
- Original Laws 1872 Chapters 776-887, 13036-78 (Volume 441)
- Original Laws 1873 Chapters 1-121, 13036-78 (Volume 442)
- Original Laws 1873 Chapters 122-265, 13036-78 (Volume 443)
- Original Laws 1873 Chapters 266-385, 13036-78 (Volume 444)
- Original Laws 1873 Chapters 386-505, 13036-78 (Volume 445)
- Original Laws 1873 Chapters 506-639, 13036-78 (Volume 446)
- Original Laws 1873 Chapters 640-777, 13036-78 (Volume 447)
- Original Laws 1873 Chapters 778-873, 13036-78 (Volume 448)
- Original Laws 1874 Chapters 1- 174, 13036-78 (Volume 449)
- Original Laws 1874 Chapters 175-321, 13036-78 (Volume 450)
- Original Laws 1874 Chapters 322-445, 13036-78 (Volume 451)
- Original Laws 1874 Chapters 446-557, 13036-78 (Volume 452)
- Original Laws 1874 Chapters 558-656, 13036-78 (Volume 453)
- Original Laws 1875 Chapters 1-176, 13036-78 (Volume 454)
- Original Laws 1875 Chapters 177-324, 13036-78 (Volume 455)
- Original Laws 1875 Chapters 325-418, 13036-78 (Volume 456)
- Original Laws 1875 Chapters 419-568, 13036-78 (Volume 457)
- Original Laws 1875 Chapters 569-634, 13036-78 (Volume 458)
- Original Laws 1876 Chapters 1-180, 13036-78 (Volume 459)
- Original Laws 1876 Chapters 181-336, 13036-78 (Volume 460)
- Original Laws 1876 Chapters 337-447, 13036-78 (Volume 461)
- Original Laws 1876 Chapters 448-449, 13036-78 (Volume 462)
- Original Laws 1877 Chapters 1-169, 13036-78 (Volume 463)
- Original Laws 1877 Chapters 170-333, 13036-78 (Volume 464)
- Original Laws 1877 Chapters 334-475, 13036-78 (Volume 465)
- Original Laws 1878 Chapters 1-161, 13036-78 (Volume 467)
- Original Laws 1878 Chapters 162-269, 13036-78 (Volume 468)
- Original Laws 1878 Chapters 270-418, 13036-78 (Volume 469)
- Original Laws 1879 Chapters 1-118, 13036-78 (Volume 470)
- Original Laws 1879 Chapters 119-240, 13036-78 (Volume 471)
- Original Laws 1879 Chapters 241-411, 13036-78 (Volume 472)
- Original Laws 1879 Chapters 412-542, 13036-78 (Volume 473)
- Original Laws 1880 Chapters 96-246, 13036-78 (Volume 475)
- Original Laws 1880 Chapters 247-376, 13036-78 (Volume 476)
- Original Laws 1880 Chapters 377-521, 13036-78 (Volume 477)
- Original Laws 1880 Chapters 522-598, 13036-78 (Volume 478)
- Original Laws 1881 Chapters 1-153, 13036-78 (Volume 479)
- Original Laws 1881 Chapters 154-282, 13036-78 (Volume 480)
- Original Laws 1881 Chapter 178 Civil Procedure, 13036-78 (Volume 481)
- Original Laws 1881 Chapters 283-417, 13036-78 (Volume 482)
- Original Laws 1881 Chapter 442 Criminal Procedure, 13036-78 (Volume 483)
- Original Laws 1881 Chapter 676 Penal Code, 13036-78 (Volume 484)
- Original Laws 1881 Chapters 418-538, 13036-78 (Volume 485)
- Original Laws 1881 Chapters 539-708, 13036-78 (Volume 486)
- Original Laws 1882 Chapters 1-124, 13036-78 (Volume 487)
- Original Laws 1882 Chapters 125-262, 13036-78 (Volume 488)
- Original Laws 1882 Chapters 263-359, 13036-78 (Volume 489)
- Original Laws 1882 Chapters 360-409, 13036-78 (Volume 490)
- Original Laws 1882 Chapter 410, 13036-78 (Volume 491)
- Original Laws 1883 Chapters 1-135, 13036-78 (Volume 492)
- Original Laws 1883 Chapters 136-257, 13036-78 (Volume 493)
- Original Laws 1883 Chapters 258-318, 13036-78 (Volume 494)
- Original Laws 1883 Chapters 319-439, 13036-78 (Volume 495)
- Original Laws 1883 Chapters 440-523, 13036-78 (Volume 496)
- Original Laws 1884 Chapters 1-165, 13036-78 (Volume 497)
- Original Laws 1884 Chapters 166-296, 13036-78 (Volume 498)
- Original Laws 1884 Chapters 297-465, 13036-78 (Volume 499)
- Original Laws 1884 Chapters 466-551, 13036-78 (Volume 500)
- Original Laws 1885 Chapters 1-103, 13036-78 (Volume 501)
- Original Laws 1885 Chapters 104-220, 13036-78 (Volume 502)
- Original Laws 1885 Chapters 221-333, 13036-78 (Volume 503)
- Original Laws 1885 Chapters 334-439, 13036-78 (Volume 504)
- Original Laws 1885 Chapters 440-557, 13036-78 (Volume 505)
- Original Laws 1886 Chapters 1-117, 13036-78 (Volume 506)
- Original Laws 1886 Chapters 118-228, 13036-78 (Volume 507)
- Original Laws 1886 Chapters 229-373, 13036-78 (Volume 508)
- Original Laws 1886 Chapters 374-542, 13036-78 (Volume 509)
- Original Laws 1886 Chapters 543-681, 13036-78 (Volume 510)
- Original Laws 1887 Chapters 1-133, 13036-78 (Volume 511)
- Original Laws 1887 Chapters 134-250, 13036-78 (Volume 512)
- Original Laws 1887 Chapters 251-383, 13036-78 (Volume 513)
- Original Laws 1887 Chapters 384-500, 13036-78 (Volume 514)
- Original Laws 1887 Chapters 501-594, 13036-78 (Volume 515)
- Original Laws 1887 Chapters 595-724, 13036-78 (Volume 516)
- Original Laws 1888 Chapters 1-119, 13036-78 (Volume 517)
- Original Laws 1888 Chapters 120-213, 13036-78 (Volume 518)
- Original Laws 1888 Chapters 214-295, 13036-78 (Volume 519)
- Original Laws 1888 Chapters 296-431, 13036-78 (Volume 520)
- Original Laws 1888 Chapters 432-550, 13036-78 (Volume 521)
- Original Laws 1888 Chapters 551-586, 13036-78 (Volume 522)
- Original Laws 1889 Chapters 1-125, 13036-78 (Volume 523)
- Original Laws 1889 Chapters 126-257, 13036-78 (Volume 524)
- Original Laws 1889 Chapters 258-356, 13036-78 (Volume 525)
- Original Laws 1889 Chapters 357-470, 13036-78 (Volume 526)
- Original Laws 1889 Chapters 471-570, 13036-78 (Volume 527)
- Original Laws 1890 Chapters 1-58, 13036-78 (Volume 528)
- Original Laws 1890 Chapters 59-153, 13036-78 (Volume 529)
- Original Laws 1890 Chapters 154-286, 13036-78 (Volume 530)
- Original Laws 1890 Chapters 287-367, 13036-78 (Volume 531)
- Original Laws 1890 Chapters 368-486, 13036-78 (Volume 532)
- Original Laws 1890 Chapters 487-561, 13036-78 (Volume 533)
- Original Laws 1890 Chapters 562-569, 13036-78 (Volume 534)
- Original Laws 1891 Chapters 1-104, 13036-78 (Volume 535)
- Original Laws 1891 Chapters 105-175, 13036-78 (Volume 536)
- Original Laws 1891 Chapters 176-293, 13036-78 (Volume 537)
- Original Laws 1891 Chapters 294-389, 13036-78 (Volume 538)
- Original Laws 1892 Chapters 1-143, 13036-78 (Volume 539)
- Original Laws 1892 Chapters 144-293, 13036-78 (Volume 540)
- Original Laws 1892 Chapters 294-451, 13036-78 (Volume 541)
- Original Laws 1892 Chapters 452-658, 13036-78 (Volume 542)
- Original Laws 1892 Chapters 659-679, 13036-78 (Volume 543)
- Original Laws 1892 Chapters 680-688, 13036-78 (Volume 544)
- Original Laws 1892 Chapters 689-747, 13036-78 (Volume 545)
- Original Laws 1893 Chapters 1-229, 13036-78 (Volume 546)
- Original Laws 1893 Chapters 230-414, 13036-78 (Volume 547)
- Original Laws 1893 Chapters 415-576, 13036-78 (Volume 548)
- Original Laws 1893 Chapters 577-726, 13036-78 (Volume 549)
- Original Laws 1894 Chapters 1-224, 13036-78 (Volume 550)
- Original Laws 1894 Chapters 225-427, 13036-78 (Volume 551)